Guide to the Annina Nosei Gallery Archive 1963-2009 MSS.298
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Exhibition Records, 1980-2009
  - Subseries E: Exhibitions; October 1992 - Jan 1993 - 94 - 96
    - [Gian Marco Montesano], 1992 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - ["Who's Afraid of Marcel Duchamp, Minimalism and Passport Photography"], 1992 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Subseries F: Exhibitions Record; Jan 1997 - Dec 1999
    - [List of Binder Contents], undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - [James Aldridge; Fernando Canovas; Group Exhibition; Jose Bedia], 1999 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - [Abraham David Christian], 1999 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - [Myriam Laplante; Liliana Porter; "Filtered Components"; Vincent Gallo; Arturo Elizondo], 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - [Santolo de Luca], 1998 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - [Deborah Turbeville], 1998 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - [Gallery Artists; Jenny Watson; Fernando Canovas], 1998 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - [Ghada Amer], 1998 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - ["Magiciens de la Terre"], 1998 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - [Martin G. Larralde; Graciela Hasper], 1997, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - [Winter Group Exhibition], 1997 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - [Pablo Siquier], 1997 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - [Danielle Galliano], 1997 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - [Summer Group Show], 1997 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - [Fabian Burgos], 1997 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - [Shirin Neshat; Arturo Duclos], 1997 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - [Fernando Canovas; Teresa Serrano; Group Drawing Exhibition], 1997 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - [Photocopy of Back of Unidentified Studio Anna Nosei Roma Postcard], undated (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Subseries G: Exhibition Records Jan. 2000 -
    - [Front Pocket including List of Binder Contents], undated (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - [Leemour Pelli; Izumi Chiraluce], 2008, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - [Gian Marco Montesano; Myriam Laplante; "Everland"], 2008, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - [Heidi McFall; Kocheisen + Hullman; Michelle Mercurio; Tsibi Geva], 2005 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - [Lucia Warck Meister; Phillip Toledano; Arturo Elizondo; Liliana Porter; "Young Miami"], 2004 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - [Summer Group Show; Marta Maria Perez Bravo; Jenny Watson; Ieva Mediodia; Federico Uribe], 2004 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - [Frederico Uribe; James Rosenquist; Group Show; Heidi McFall; Group Exhibition], 2003 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - [Paolo W Tamburella; Federico Uribe; Summer Group Exhibition; Myriam Laplante; Heidi McFall; David Bowes; Liliana Porter], 2002 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - [Arturo Elizondo; Jose Bedia; Tsibi Geva; Summer Group Exhibition; Paolo W. Tamburella; Tristiano Di Robilant; Group Exhibition; Jenny Watson], 2001 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - [Gernot Linder, Carole Benzaken; Cemin, Christian, Schwart, Federico Uribe; Graciela Hasper; Summer Invitational; Liliana Porter], 2000 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - [Marta Maria Perez Bravo; Kocheisen + Hullmann; Fabian Burgos; Group Photography Exhibition], 1999, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - [Back Pocket], 2000 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Subseries H: Catalogs
    Subseries comprises catalogs of artists and artists' works produced regularly by the Annina Nosei Gallery. Catalogs come in the following categories: Individual Artists, "Group Shows," "7 Latin American Artists," "The Door," and Occasional Compilations of exhibitions over a span of three to five years, each of which is described as "a testimony recording a seletion of the artist I have worked with during the last three [or "five"] years."
    Subseries is arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically within the same year.
    - Group Shows, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Chuck Connelly, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - The Door, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Vincent Gallo, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Claudio Palmeri, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - [Occasional Compilations] [1/2], 1986-1998 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - [Occasional Compilations] [2/2], 1998-2006 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Beth Brenner, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Helmut Middendorf, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Tsibi Geva, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Julio Galan, 1990-1996 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Jenny Watson, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Gian Marco Montesano, 1991, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 7 Latin American Artists, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Teresa Serrano, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Stephen Mueller, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Shirin Neshat, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Myriam Leplante, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Arturo Elizondo, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Heidi McFall [1/2], 2002-2005 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Heidi McFall [2/2], 2008 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Subseries I: Guest Books
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [1], 1994 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [2], 1994, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [3], 1995, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [4], 1996, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [5], 1997 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [6], 1997 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - [Spiral-Bound Guestbook] [1], 1997, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - [Spiral-Bound Guestbook] [2], 1998 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - [Loose Paper from "Spiral-Bound Guestbook [2]"], 1998 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - [Spiral-Bbound Guestbook] [3], 1998 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - [Perfect-Bound Guestbook] [7], 1998, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Other Administrative Files, 1978-2009
  Series comprises material related to the general day-to-day administration of the gallery itself and the gallery space.
  - Subseries A: Planners
    Subseries is arranged chronologically. Interleaved material photocopied to indicated original location. Original and photocopy are placed in back of folder.
    - [1978, 1988 Planner] (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - [1982 Planner] (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - [1989, 1991 Planner] (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - [1993 Planner] (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - [2005 Planner] (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Memos
    - Memos [Apr 28, 1998 - Jun9, 1998] (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Memos [Jun 19, 1998 - Aug 7, 1998] (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Memos [Sept 2, 1998 - Dec 17, 1998] (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Memos [Jan 15, 1999 - May 27, 1999] (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Memos [June 29, 1999 - Oct 10, 1999] (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Memos [Oct 19, 1999 - Dec 21, 1999] (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Memos [Jan 4, 2000 - Mar 28, 2000] (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Memos [Apr 4, 2000 - May 16, 2000] (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Memos [May 30, 2000 - Sept 26, 2000] (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Memos [Oct 17, 2000 - Dec. 12, 2000] (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Memos [Jan 2, 2001 - Mar 26, 2001] (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Memos [Mar 27, 2001 - May 8, 2001] (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Memos [Jul 2, 2001 - Oct 11, 2001] (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Memos [Oct 30, 2001 - Dec 11, 2001] (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Memos [Jan 8, 2002 - Apr 9, 2002] (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Memos [Apr 30, 2002 - Sep 17, 2002] (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Memos [Oct 1, 2002 - Dec 17, 2002] (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Memos [Jan 8, 2003 - Nov 28, 2003] (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Memos [Jan 7, 2004 - Mar 2, 2004] (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Memos [March 9, 2004 - June 1, 2004] (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Memos [June 14, 2004 - Dec 21, 2004] (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Memos [Jan 5, 2005 - May 10, 2005] (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Memos [May 24, 2005 - Oct 4, 2005] (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Memos [Oct 6, 2005 - Dec 19, 2005] (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Memos [Jan 12, 2006 - Oct 23, 2006; Mar 5, 2007 - July 12, 2007], 2006, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Memos [June 26, 2008 - Jan 12, 2009], 2008, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Memos [Fax from Lee Ortega to Mitchell Langsner], undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Memos [Exhibition Cards for Jenny Watson, Helmut Middendorf, Patrick Grant], 1990, 1991, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Subseries C: Gallery Space
    - Fire 88', 1988 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      Folder contains documents and photographs relating to a 1988 fire at the gallery. It was originally filed at the end of Series II, Subseries E, and remains physically in its original place (box 23, folder 9).
- Series VII: Pre-gallery Curating, 1977-1978
  Before opening her own gallery, Annina Nosei curated exhibitions at various locations. Series comprises material drawn from the exhibitions "Discussions," "Painting," "Memory," "Angelo Savelli: Paintings & Sculpture," and comprises press releases, programs, brochures, artist bios, and an essay by Annina Nosei on Savelli.
  - Pre-Gallery Curating, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Series VIII: Misc. Periodicals and Clippings, undated
  Materials were originally grouped by artist and shelved in magazine files bearing the artist's name. That grouping is preserved, and the folder titles bear the original labels of the magazine files.
  The folder "Jose Bedia [/Guillermo Kuitca]" contains material related to both Bedia and Kuitca though the original folder only listed Bedia's name.
  Series comprises some monographs of artists represented by the gallery, some periodicals that include artists represented by the gallery, and various clippings, all accumulated and stored by the gallery.
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 39)
    Fabian Burgos, Graciela Hasper, Tsibi Geva, Julio Galan, Jose Bedia, Guillermo Kuitca
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 40)
    Jose Bedia, Guillermo Kuitca, Arturo Elizando, Kocheisen + Hullman, Myriam Laplant, Jenny Watson, David Bowes, Helmut Middendorf
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 41)
    Shirin Neshat, Liliana Porter, Salomé, Bernd Koberling, Arturo Duclos, Manuel Ocampo
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 42)
    Liliana Porter, Jenny Watson, Karel Appel, David Bowes, Nancy Bowen, Keith Milow, David Deutsch, Pierre and Giles, Colombo
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 43)
    Daniele Galliano, Sabina Mirri, Marco Montesano, Mimmo Paladino, Cheri Samba
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 44)
    Ellen Brooks, Pizzi Cannella, De Luca, Gilardi, Commandeur, Welch, Amer, Ongaro, David Bowes, Gallo, Schuyff, Varejao, Paparatti, Chuck Connelly, Palmieri, Marco Tirelli, Nunzio
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 45)
    Cheri Samba, Chritiane Richter, Teresa Serrano, Salomé, Castelli, Graciela Hasper, Adriana Varejao, K.H. Hodicke, Maurizio Pellegrin, Peter Schuyff Monika Bravo, Abraham David Christian,
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 46)
    Roger Welch, Lucia Warck Meister, Arturo Duclos, Sabina Mirri, Janieta Eyre, Pizzi Cannella, Nunzio, Jeff Wall, Chuck Connelly, Anna Papratti, Miscellaneous Publications
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 47)
    Miscellaneous Publications
  - Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, undated (Box 11)
  - [Concept Image Acoustique], 1996 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Format: Compact disks.
    Disk was loose with miscellaneous artist publications. Moved to separate box for preservation.
- Oversize Series II: Correspondence, 1981, 2001-2002
  - Oversize Subseries A: General Artist Files
    - E, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Note: There is no Folder 1 for box 53. Folder 2 is the first folder.
    - Steve Shane, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Oversize Subseries C: Museums and Universities
    - Lannan Foundation, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1982 (Folder 11)
  - Oversize Subseries D: Art Fairs/Auction Houses
    - Young Miami, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Documenta: "FIAC 90-1991", undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Gudaljar: "Venezia Biennale [...]", undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Sotheby's: "[Untitled]", undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Basel Art Fari - June 1994/95[99] (Folder 10)
  - Oversize Subseries E: Magazines, Critics, and Curators
    - Artforum, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Art in America, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - D, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series III: Artist Files, 1969, 1980-1999
  - Oversize Subseries A: General Artist Files
    - Sandro Chia, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Julio Galan - Press Articles, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Vincent Gallo - Press Original [From "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Piero Gilardi, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - K.D. Hodicke, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Massimo Kaufman, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Gary Lang, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Sabina Mirri, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Olivier Mosset, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Stephen Mueller [1], 1990 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Shirin Neshat [1/2], 1995 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Mimmo Paladino, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Rammellzee, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Lia Rumma, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - [Loose Material from "Salome and Castelli" Letter Box], 1982 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box], 1981 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - John Ahearn, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Jean-Michel Alberola, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Ghada Amer, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - [Basquiat], 1981, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Jose Marie Bermejo, 1980-1984 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Francois Boisrond, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Nancy Bowen - Press, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - David Bowes - Press + Correspondence, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Beth Brenner, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - C, 1981, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Pizzi Cannella - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Bruno Ceccobelli [2], 1991 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Chuck Connelly, 1982, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Chuck Connelly - Press [From "Chuck Connelly 1989" Letter Box], 1984 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - G, undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - $$ Julio Galan Accounting, undated (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Vincent Gallo [Folder from "Vincent Gallo" Letter Box], 1999 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - B [Mike Glier] [From Untitled Letter Box #2], undated (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - I/J, 1981-1983 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Barbara Kruger [Binder] [1], 1985 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Barbara Kruger [1/2], 1983, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Barbara Kruger - Press [2/2], 1986 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Barbara Kruger - Reviews, undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Correspondence, undated (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Guillermo Kuitca: Press, undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Allan McCollum, 1987, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Hanging Instructions for Allan McCollum "200 Plastic Surrogates", undated (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Keith Milow, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - [Shirin Neshat - Anouncements], 1997 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Donald Newman, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Claudio Palmieri, 1986, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - A [From "Salomé + Castelli" Letter Box], 1981 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Teresa Serano, 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Randy Stevens, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Adriana Varejao, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Tod Wizon, 1984-1987 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Veronique Bellavista, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Mike Glier - Downstairs [From Untitled Letter Box #2], undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - [Mike Glier] [Loose Material from Untitled Letter Box #2], 1981-1983 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - S [Mike Glier] [From Untitled Letter Box #2], undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Lynn Hirshman [Letter Box], undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Barbara Kruger Announcements, 1982-1986 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Stephen Mueller [2], 1986, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - David Salle, 1979-1982 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Cheri Samba, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Suzanne Santoro, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Mario Schifano, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Tatafiore [Letter Box], 1980, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Jenny Watson, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Ellen Brooks [2], undated (Folder 1 Left)
    - [Loose Material from "Deutsch" Letter Box], 1981-1983 (Folder 9)
    - E. Mattacci, 1983 (Folder 8)
  - Oversize Subseries E: Material Separated from Visuals Binders
    - Fernando Canovas [From Front Pocket], undated (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Fernando Canovas [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 6/28], undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Fernando Canovas [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 7/28], undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Fernando Canovas [1/2] [Binder Sleeve 8/28], undated (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Paul D. Miller/Gian Marco Montesano [From Binder Sleeve 8/8, undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Ceccobelli; Chia; Commandeur; Colombo, undated (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Pietro Fortuna; Tomarchio Levi; Ronald Gault Jirado [Back Pocket], undated (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Mary Oberling; Beth Brenner [Front Pocket], undated (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Front Pocket], undated (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Salomé; Castelli [Back Pocket], undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Fabian Burgos/Graciela Hasper, undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Oversize Series IV: Jean-Michel Basquiat Artist File, undated
  - Oversize Subseries A: Artist Files
    - Jean-Michel Basquiat Press, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Subseries C: Accounting
    - [Contents of Plastic Sleeve from "Accounting Jean Michel Basquiat [1/3]"], undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Subseries J: Periodicals Clippings
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [1/3], undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [2/3], undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [3/3], undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [1/3], undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - [Oversive Periodicals] [2/3], undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [Oversize Periodicals] [3/3], undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series V: Exhibition Records, undated
  - Subseries A: Annina Nosei Gallery Shows; 1982-1983, 1983-1984
    - [Barbara Kruger], undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Oversize Series VI: Other Administrative Files, undated
  - Oversize Subseries C: Gallery Space
    - [530 West 22nd Street Gallery Floor Plan], undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Oversize Series VIII: Misc. Artist Publications, Periodicals, Clippings, 1981-2004
  - Jose Bedia [/Guillermo Kuitca] [Oversize] [1/2], 1992, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - [Arturo Duclos], 1995 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Julio Galan [Folder "Mastering Millenn. May 9-Aug 9 1999], 1992-1999 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Kocheisen + Hullman [Oversize] [1/2], undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - [Myriam] Laplante, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Helmut Middendorf, 1989, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Mirri, 1983, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - [Manuel Ocampo], 1994 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - [Petery Schyff], 1987 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [1/4], undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Appel; Bowes; Bowen; Pierre; Milow; Abor. Art, [Colombo, Deutsch], 1985 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - E. Brooks, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Julio Galan, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Kocheisen + Hullman [Oversize] [2/2], 2003, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - [Poster Interleaved in "Ein Anders Klima/A Different Climate" in [?] Folder], undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Samba, 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [2/4], 1981 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [3/4], 1988, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications] [4/4], undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Tsibi Geva, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Sandro Chia, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Liliana Porter, 1991-2003 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - [Oversize Miscellaneous Publications], undated (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Jose Bedia [/Guillermo Kuitca], undated (Folder 7)
  - Kruger, undated (Folder 6)
- Accretion 2011 - Series I: Transaction Records, 1983-2003
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries A: Consignment Files
    Chronological
    - In on Consignment Returned 1989, 1987-1989 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - In on Consignment Returned 1990, 1989-1993 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Out on Consignment Returned 1990 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - In on Consignment Returned 1991 & 1992 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - In on Consignment 1991-92-93, 1991-1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Consignments, 1996-2003 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Old Consignments, 1997-2003 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries F: Artist Books
    - Post Sales - Records Works Sold in Prince Street in the 1980s, 1983-1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      This folder contains loose leaf sheets with the same information that might be found in an Artist Book (what works by what artists are sold to what collectors, galleries, etc.).
- Accretion 2011 - Series II: Correspondence, 1980-2005
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries D: Art Fairs/Auction Houses
    - Young Miami, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries E: Magazines, Critics, and Curators
    - E-Bay, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      Includes an invitation to Kim Leven to attend the opening of a Julio Galan show.
    - Ads, 2004, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Includes some material that could be Series I Subseries A, Series II Subseries C, and Series VI Subseries A.
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries F: Misc. Accretion Correspondence
    This subseries was created for some accretion correspondence that was neither originally organized as nor fits in any of the Subseries A-E under Series II.
    Chrono
    - Fine Art Conservation Inc., 1980-1983, 1990-1991, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - [Letter from Chicago Clearing Corporation], 2005 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Accretion 2011 - Series III: Artist Files, 1999, 2005
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries A: General Artist Files
    Alphabetical by folder label
    - British Artists, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      Includes material on the artist David Perry and correspondence regarding some damaged prints by Lucia Pearsey.
    - [Loose Material - List of Gallery Artists], undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Artist's Bios, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Accretion 2011 - Series V: Exhibition Records, 1980-2004
  The folders in this accretion series and subseries are placed here by the archivist; they were not received in binders as were the first accession fo Exhibition Records. On examining the contents of each folder the archivist determined that the contents of each seemed to fit in with the material in Series V.
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries J: Accretion Exhibition Records
    - Press Releases, 1980-1984 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Price Lists 1980; 1984-1986-87, 1980-1987 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Press Release 1984-1986-1987, 1983-1987, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Group Shows, 1985-2002 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Group Shows, 1991-1999 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Photography Show 12/99, 1997-2000 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Magiciens de la Terre [1/2], 1998 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Magiciens de la Terre [2/2] [Binder and Contents of Front and Back Pockets], undated (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Dec. 16th Show w/Richard M.; Group/Winter, 2000-2001 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - [July 11-October 15, 2002 Group Exhibition Checklist] (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Robert Miller Gallery Nov 2003 Rosenquist Show, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Cocktail Party - Bronx Museum, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Accretion 2011 - Series VI: Other Administrative Files, 1992-2000
  - Accretion 2011 - Subseries B: Memos
    - Memos [Loose Material from 1994-1995 Folder], undated (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Memos [Jan 24, 1992 - May 13, 1994]], 1992-1994 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Memos [May 27, 1994 - Sep 30, 1994] (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Memos [Jan 7, 1995 - June 23, 1995] (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Memos [June 30, 1995 - Mar 19, 1996], 1995-1996 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Memos [Apr 4, 1996 - Oct 29, 1996] (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Memos [Nov 5, 1996 - Feb 18, 1997], 1996-1997 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Memos [Feb 25, 1997 - June 18, 1997] (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Memos [July 7, 1997 - Dec 16, 1997] (Box 56 a, Folder 1)
    - Memos [Jan 13, 1998 - May 14, 1998] (Box 56 a, Folder 2)